<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Infrastructure on Red Hat Telco Tigers Repository</title><link>https://rh-telco-tigers.github.io/infrastructure/</link><description>Recent content in Infrastructure on Red Hat Telco Tigers Repository</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 16:53:26 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rh-telco-tigers.github.io/infrastructure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploying an overcloud in OCP with Openstack Director Operator (OSPdO)</title><link>https://rh-telco-tigers.github.io/infrastructure/ospdo-tutorial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 16:53:26 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://rh-telco-tigers.github.io/infrastructure/ospdo-tutorial/</guid><description>This tutorial aims to provide an OpenStack deployment procedure using the OpenStack director operator on OpenShift, utilizing minimal OpenStack templates and steps. The tutorial is based on OpenStack 17.1.
Blog GitHub Repo</description></item><item><title>BGP Peering with Juniper CN2</title><link>https://rh-telco-tigers.github.io/infrastructure/bgp-peering-junipercn2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:01:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://rh-telco-tigers.github.io/infrastructure/bgp-peering-junipercn2/</guid><description>Dive into the implementation of CN2 (Juniper Cloud-Native Container Network) as the Container Networking Interface (CNI) in OpenShift. By enabling IP forwarding, this allowed pods and services in the namespace to communicate with an external router through CN2&amp;rsquo;s fabric forwarding feature over BGP.
Blog Article Blog GitHub Repo</description></item><item><title>Control Runtime of AWS Demo Clusters</title><link>https://rh-telco-tigers.github.io/infrastructure/control-runtime-aws-clusters/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rh-telco-tigers.github.io/infrastructure/control-runtime-aws-clusters/</guid><description>OCP AWS Miser contains a set of ansible scripts taht can be used to power off, and power on an OpenShift cluster. You can schedule these scripts to run via cron or form AAP to control when a DEMO OpenShift cluster is running in the AWS cloud. By only running the OCP demo environment durring normal business hours M-F, you can save over 75% of the cost of running the cluster full time for a month.</description></item><item><title>Managing Ocp Infrastructures Using Gitops</title><link>https://rh-telco-tigers.github.io/infrastructure/managing-ocp-infrastructures-using-gitops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 14:00:55 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://rh-telco-tigers.github.io/infrastructure/managing-ocp-infrastructures-using-gitops/</guid><description>This multi-part blog series will cover how to deploy bare-metal server resources into an OCP cluster using Gitops tooling
In the first part of this series, I showed you how the to install the Assisted Service/CIM (Central Infrastructure Management) and how a cluster can be deployed in a declarative manner using approximately 9 YAML files.
Part 1 of Article Gitops-Blog GitHub Repo
In the second part of this series, we could see how that YAML files could be condensed into a single SiteConfig file.</description></item><item><title>Backup Restore Etcd State</title><link>https://rh-telco-tigers.github.io/infrastructure/backup-restore-etcd-state/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 13:43:13 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://rh-telco-tigers.github.io/infrastructure/backup-restore-etcd-state/</guid><description>This article describes the steps necessary to backup and restore the etcd state on an OCP cluster. The article was written based on version 4.6 of OCP but is still relevent. There are also accompanying videos that show these processes.
Backup and Restore of ETCD State</description></item></channel></rss>